(Raj:)the probe will have arrived
(Raj:)in perfect working order.
(Howard:)So, in addition to being crazy,
you're resting the fate
(Howard:)of the mission
on your athletic prowess.
(Leonard:)Yes.
(Howard:)The man who crashed
his stationary bike.
(Raj:)I didn't crash it, okay?
(Raj:)My playlist was too up-tempo,
(Raj:)I got light-headed
and I fell off.
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Raj:)It all...
(Raj:)comes down...
(Raj:)to this.
(Howard:)You happy? Now you can relax.
(Raj:)What kind of scientist are you?
Everyone knows
(Raj:)you got to make
two out of three.
(Leonard:)This isn't so bad.
(Sheldon:)That's easy for you to say.
(Sheldon:)Your chair's not
facing the lingerie section.
(Sheldon:)Boy, that's a lot of panties.